Hello friends, welcome to a new video from Stock Market STV.
In this video, "Swing Trade Opportunity," we'll
discuss three stocks
and explore their potential opportunities.
Friends, my sole
request is that you watch this video fully
and fully before we proceed.
If you haven't yet subscribed to our channel, please
press our "+" button to receive notifications of upcoming videos.
If you enjoy this video and
find it informative, please
like, comment, and share. Our
first stock today is III Lord General Insurance
Company Limited,
a mid-cap company with a market cap of ₹67,649 crore.
This stock closed at ₹5,445 on Wednesday, January 17,
2024,
and technically,
the stock appears to be trading strong. Its
52-week high is ₹1,492, and its 52-
week low is ₹
1,095. The stock has recently traded at
₹1,353.  After taking support around ₹1,472 and 35 paise, it has now
started showing indications of an up move. Now
its target which is emerging is
its first resistance of ₹1,472 and 35
paise. Its second resistance is ₹
1,4931 paise and its third resistance is ₹
1,53225 paise. If this stock is
able to continue its move, then in the coming time,
this stock can be seen touching these levels or
even going above these levels.
And if this stock goes down from this level, then
its first support will be ₹
1,4365 paise, its second support will be ₹
1,4124 paise and its third support will be ₹
1,375 and 90 paise. Entry can be made in this stock by keeping stop loss at 1 or 2 or at the
first support,
slightly above or below the last closing price, as per
your analysis. So,
our
second stock today is Mishra Dhatu Nigam Limited.
It is
a small stock with a market cap of ₹7680 crore.
This stock is a CAP company. It closed at ₹33.25 on Wednesday, January 17,
2024,
and as of now, the
stock appears to be strengthening. The
stock's 52-week high
is ₹7670 and 252-week low
is ₹17225.
After taking support around ₹93 in recent days, the stock has now
started showing indications of an up move. Now,
its target that is emerging is
its first resistance of ₹
444.80, its second resistance of ₹6220
and its third resistance of ₹
77.4. If this stock is
able to continue its move, then in the coming time,
this stock can be seen touching these levels or
going above these levels.
If this stock goes down from this level, then
its first support will be at
₹2500000 or at 1 or 2 levels. [Music]  By
placing a stop-loss at support, an entry can be made
slightly above or below the last closing price, or
based on your analysis.
Our third stock today is GR
Infra Projects Limited. It is
a small-cap company with a market cap of ₹1116 crore.
This stock
closed at ₹1 and 85 paise on Wednesday, January 17, 2024, and
technically, this stock appears to be strengthening. The
stock's 52-week high is ₹1,381,
and 52-week low is ₹930.
After taking support around ₹6 in recent days, the stock has now
started showing indications of an up move. Now,
its target emerging is
its first resistance of ₹
901 paise, its second resistance of ₹
10,292 paise, and its third resistance of ₹
1,2265 and 15 paise. If this stock is
able to continue its move, then in the coming times,
this stock can be seen touching these levels or
even moving above these levels.  It can come
and if this stock goes below this level
then its first support will be ₹1
22.95 paise, its second support will be
8230 paise and its third support will be
0338 paise. Entry can be made in this stock at one or two levels or at the
first support by keeping the stop loss a
little above or below the last closing price
or as per your analysis.
Friends, this
video is only and only for educational purpose. There is no
buy, sell or hold
advice in it. You are advised to
consult your financial advisor before trading.
Thanks for watching the video friends, we will meet in our next
video, till then goodbye.